Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[The following events are a work of fiction.
[الأحداث التالية هي عمل خيالي.
The characters' names, behaviors, and actions are not related to any institution,
أسماء الشخصيات، وسلوكياتها، وأفعالها لا ترتبط بأي مؤسسة،
organization, or profession, and are created for entertainment purposes only.
المنظمة أو المهنة، ويتم إنشاؤها لأغراض الترفيه فقط.
Viewer discretion is advised]
يُنصح المشاهد بتوخي الحذر
I killed someone.
لقد قتلت شخصا ما.
[Rabid Dog]
[كلب مسعور]
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Applying an under-eye mask.
تطبيق قناع تحت العين.
You're already gorgeous.
أنت جميلة بالفعل.
Where are you going, sis?
إلى أين تذهبين يا أختي؟
Shhh!
شششش!
See you.
أرك لاحقًا.
Huh?
هاه؟
I'll be going now.
سأذهب الآن.
Where are you going this time?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب هذه المرة؟
You dropped out
لقد تركت الدراسة
and said you'd look for work.
وقال أنك سوف تبحث عن عمل.
All you do is drink.
كل ما عليك فعله هو الشرب.
I've talked to my friends.
لقد تحدثت مع أصدقائي.
I'm going to buy and sell secondhand clothes.
سأقوم بشراء وبيع الملابس المستعملة.
Don't worry about me.
لا تقلق علي.
Why can't you be a good example for Cream for once?
لماذا لا يمكنك أن تكون مثالاً جيدًا لكريم ولو لمرة واحدة؟
All you do is frivolous stuff.
كل ما تفعله هو أشياء تافهة.
Cream and I are different, Dad.
أنا وكريم مختلفان يا أبي.
If she loves studying, then let her be.
إذا كانت تحب الدراسة، فلتكن كذلك.
I don't.
أنا لا.
Selling secondhand goods?
بيع البضائع المستعملة؟
Sneaking out at night to drink?
التسلل خارجا في الليل للشرب؟
This is how you're gonna live?
هكذا ستعيش؟
Then I'm sorry
ثم أنا آسف
for failing to be the good girl you expect me to be.
لأنني فشلت في أن أكون الفتاة الطيبة التي تتوقعين مني أن أكونها.
Cheers! Cheers!
هتاف! هتاف!
Guys, you're drunk already?
يا شباب، هل أنتم في حالة سُكر بالفعل؟
Your faces are all red!
وجوهكم كلها حمراء!
I'm kidding.
أنا أمزح.
Just a bit more, come on.
فقط قليلًا، هيا.
- Hey, guys... - Wait, cheers!
- مرحبًا يا شباب... - انتظروا، هتافات!
Watch your step.
انتبه لخطواتك.
This way, Claire!
من هنا، كلير!
Claire.
كلير.
I'm home.
أنا الوطن.
Aww, I'm actually craving this.
أوه، أنا في الواقع أتوق إلى هذا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Have you had anything?
هل لديك أي شيء؟
I haven't, actually.
لم أفعل ذلك في الواقع.
Gosh.
يا إلهي.
You carry these every day?
هل تحمل هذه الأشياء كل يوم؟
Mm.
مم.
Currently, I'm preparing for the International Physics Olympiad.
أقوم حاليًا بالتحضير لأولمبياد الفيزياء الدولي.
I've got subjects that I'm worried I'll be behind.
لدي مواضيع أشعر بالقلق من أنني سأكون متأخرًا فيها.
That's why I'm carrying the books around.
ولهذا السبب أحمل الكتب معي.
You're always like this.
أنت دائما هكذا.
You said you couldn't study them in time,
قلت أنك لا تستطيع دراستهم في الوقت المناسب،
but you'd always get full scores.
ولكنك ستحصل دائمًا على الدرجات الكاملة.
And...
و...
You're not going to continue your studies?
لن تستمر في دراستك؟
Probably not.
ربما لا.
I have no knack for this.
ليس لدي أي موهبة في هذا.
Honestly, you're a great student.
بصراحة أنت طالب رائع.
You learn new things so easily,
تتعلم أشياء جديدة بسهولة،
meanwhile I don't.
وفي الوقت نفسه لا أفعل ذلك.
For example?
على سبيل المثال؟
Like, riding a bicycle.
مثل ركوب الدراجة.
It took you only an hour to figure out how to ride it.
لقد استغرق الأمر ساعة واحدة فقط لمعرفة كيفية ركوبها.
The same goes for swimming.
والشيء نفسه ينطبق على السباحة.
I think you're talented.
أعتقد أنك موهوب.
Why are the examples so funny-sounding?
لماذا تبدو الأمثلة مضحكة جداً؟
Hey! They're not.
مهلا! إنهم ليسوا كذلك.
They're all survival skills.
إنها كلها مهارات البقاء.
I can't hold it anymore.
لا أستطيع التحمل أكثر من ذلك.
Hey.
يا.
Hm?
هممم؟
Do you want to know a secret?
هل تريد أن تعرف سرًا؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Promise me you won't tell anyone.
وعدني أنك لن تخبر أحدا.
I promise.
أعدك.
I actually don't have any talents.
أنا في الواقع لا أملك أية مواهب.
I just say, "Screw it.
أنا فقط أقول، "اذهب إلى الجحيم".
It's okay to fail.
لا بأس بالفشل.
I'll keep at it until I get there."
سأستمر في ذلك حتى أصل إلى هناك.
When you're not worried about making mistakes,
عندما لا تشعر بالقلق بشأن ارتكاب الأخطاء،
you'll learn things quickly.
سوف تتعلم الأشياء بسرعة.
Is the reason you're not returning to school
هل هذا هو السبب في عدم عودتك إلى المدرسة؟
that you're worried you'll do worse than me?
هل أنت قلق من أنك ستفعل ما هو أسوأ مني؟
Hey! I'm not worried about that.
مهلا! أنا لست قلقا بشأن ذلك.
- Are you? - I'm not!
- هل أنت؟ - أنا لا!
Let's just say that being a good daughter
دعنا نقول فقط أن كونك ابنة جيدة
is your duty, okay?
هذا واجبك، حسنًا؟
As for being a nonsensical daughter,
أما بالنسبة لكونها ابنة غير منطقية،
I'll take care of that.
سأعتني بهذا الأمر.
Okay?
تمام؟
Okay, I guess.
حسنًا، أعتقد ذلك.
Come on, eat up.
تعال، تناول الطعام.
I'm starving.
أنا جائع.
Let me have some of yours.
دعني آخذ بعضًا منك.
My cup is almost empty.
كأسي فارغة تقريبا.
- No! - Just a bit!
- لا! - فقط قليلا!
I refuse!
انا ارفض!
Hey, to me!
مهلا بالنسبة لي!
There!
هناك!
Teacher Maed.
المعلمة مايد.
Can you help me with the International Physics Olympiad?
هل يمكنك مساعدتي في أولمبياد الفيزياء الدولي؟
I don't accept tutoring, unfortunately.
لا أقبل الدروس الخصوصية، للأسف.
It needs school permission.
يحتاج إلى إذن المدرسة.
Please help me, Teacher.
من فضلك ساعدني يا معلم.
I really want a spot by competing in the Olympiad.
أريد حقًا الحصول على مكان في المنافسة في الأولمبياد.
If the school finds out,
إذا اكتشفت المدرسة ذلك،
I'll be in deep trouble.
سأكون في ورطة كبيرة.
I beg you, Teacher.
أتوسل إليك يا معلم.
I'll study hard and won't let you down.
سأدرس بجد ولن أخذلك.
Please, Teacher.
من فضلك يا معلم.
Fine, I'll help.
حسنًا، سأساعدك.
But you must not tell this to anybody,
ولكن لا يجب عليك أن تخبر أحدا بهذا،
okay?
تمام؟
Okay.
تمام.
Uh...
أوه...
What about the fee?
ماذا عن الرسوم؟
We'll talk about it later.
سنتحدث عن ذلك لاحقًا.
Yay!
ياي!
Thank you! Thank you so much.
شكرا جزيلا!
I'll study my heart out.
سأدرس قلبي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Have a good one, Teacher.
أتمنى لك يومًا طيبًا يا معلم.
Bye-bye.
وداعا وداعا.
A mass M with volume V is released into a deep cup of water,
يتم إطلاق كتلة M بحجم V في كوب عميق من الماء،
- right? - Yes.
- صحيح؟ - نعم.
It'd look like this, with a ping-pong ball underneath.
سيبدو الأمر بهذا الشكل، مع وجود كرة بينج بونج أسفله.
Notice that it's the same.
لاحظ أنه نفس الشيء.
The only difference is the latter.
الفرق الوحيد هو الأخير.
Great!
عظيم!
Awesome!
مذهل!
Have I kept you waiting?
هل جعلتك تنتظر؟
Hey, Claire!
مهلا، كلير!
I went and got the clothes, guys.
ذهبت وحصلت على الملابس، يا رفاق.
I think I can do this.
أعتقد أنني أستطيع فعل هذا.
Cool!
رائع!
Cheers!
هتافات!
You guys are so funny.
أنتم مضحكون جدًا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You've gotten so much better, Cream.
لقد أصبحت أفضل بكثير، كريم.
At this rate,
بهذا المعدل،
you're sure to get the quota spot.
من المؤكد أنك ستحصل على مكان الحصة.
Thank you, Teacher.
شكرا لك يا معلم.
Cream, do you know that...
كريم هل تعلم أن...
of all the students I've taught,
من بين جميع الطلاب الذين قمت بتدريسهم،
you're the most beautiful.
أنت الأجمل.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Teacher...
مدرس...
This is a bit too close.
هذا قريب قليلا.
I've helped you.
لقد ساعدتك.
Please don't do this.
من فضلك لا تفعل هذا.
Please return the favor.
من فضلك رد الجميل.
Stay still.
ابقى ساكنا.
Help!
يساعد!
Help me!
ساعدني!
I told you to stay still.
لقد قلت لك أن تبقى ساكنا.
Get back!
العودة!
Go away!
يبتعد!
- Who is it? - This song...
- من هذا؟ - هذه الأغنية...
It's Cream.
إنه كريم.
- Cream? - Who is it?
- كريم؟ - من هو؟
Oh, it's my sister.
أوه، إنها أختي.
What is it, Cream?
ما الأمر يا كريم؟
- Hey, where are you going, Claire? - Claire?
- مهلا، إلى أين أنت ذاهب، كلير؟ - كلير؟
Claire!
كلير!
Hello, Cream?
مرحبا كريم؟
Cream!
كريم!
D*mn it!
لعنة عليك!
Claire...
كلير...
Cream!
كريم!
I killed him.
لقد قتلته.
He tried to sexually assault me.
لقد حاول الاعتداء علي جنسيا.
I did it to defend myself.
لقد فعلت ذلك للدفاع عن نفسي.
I didn't mean to do it...
لم أقصد أن أفعل ذلك...
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I'll call the cops.
سأتصل بالشرطة.
Claire!
كلير!
Don't do it, please.
لا تفعل ذلك من فضلك.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Don't call the police, please.
من فضلك لا تتصل بالشرطة.
Please, can we...
من فضلك هل يمكننا...
Can we keep it a secret?
هل يمكننا أن نبقيه سرا؟
I don't want anybody to find out about this.
لا أريد لأحد أن يعرف هذا الأمر.
Please?
لو سمحت؟
Please.
لو سمحت.
He sexually assaulted me.
لقد اعتدى علي جنسيا.
Please, help me, Claire.
من فضلك ساعديني يا كلير.
Please, get me out of this.
من فضلك أخرجني من هذا.
Go home without me, okay?
اذهب إلى المنزل بدوني، حسنًا؟
I'll deal with this myself.
سأتعامل مع هذا الأمر بنفسي.
What are you going to do?
ما كنت تنوي القيام به؟
But you have to promise me
ولكن عليك أن تعدني
you won't tell this to anyone,
لن تخبر أحدا بهذا
including Mom, Dad,
بما في ذلك أمي وأبي
your close friends, or anybody.
أصدقائك المقربين، أو أي شخص.
Keep your lips sealed.
حافظ على شفتيك مغلقة.
Understood?
مفهوم؟
Promise me that this stays between us sisters.
وعدني أن هذا الأمر يبقى بيننا أخوات.
Cream!
كريم!
Promise?
يعد؟
I promise.
أعدك.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
You're a good girl...
أنت فتاة جيدة...
You have a bright future ahead of you.
لديك مستقبل مشرق أمامك.
Study hard...
ادرس بجد...
Make Mom and Dad proud.
اجعل أمي وأبي فخورين.
Understood?
مفهوم؟
What are you going to do?
ما كنت تنوي القيام به؟
It's time to leave.
حان وقت الرحيل.
Cream.
كريم.
Don't forget our promise.
لا تنسى وعدنا .
I'll see you soon.
سوف أراك قريبا.
How's it going?
كيف الحال؟
Are you alright? You look a bit off.
هل أنت بخير؟ تبدو غريبًا بعض الشيء.
The dead teacher's sister came to talk to me.
جاءت أخت المعلمة المتوفاة لتتحدث معي.
She then showed me a photo of Cream.
ثم أظهرت لي صورة كريم.
Everyone must have known
يجب أن يكون الجميع قد عرفوا
who my sister is.
من هي أختي؟
How did she know?
كيف عرفت؟
I should be the one asking you.
أنا من يجب أن يسألك.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
You're the only one I talked to about my sister,
أنت الشخص الوحيد الذي تحدثت معه عن أختي،
and then it suddenly spread around.
ثم انتشر فجأة.
Wait.
انتظر.
You think I spread the news about her?
هل تعتقد أنني نشرت الخبر عنها؟
Then who else could it be?
إذن من يمكن أن يكون غير ذلك؟
Not long ago, you were on the phone.
لم يمض وقت طويل قبل أن تتحدث على الهاتف.
Claire...
كلير...
I didn't tell anyone.
لم أخبر أحدا.
Why would I do that?
لماذا أفعل ذلك؟
Who were you talking to?
من كنت تتحدث معه؟
I called my attorney.
لقد اتصلت بمحاميي.
I wanted a new one.
أردت واحدة جديدة.
You don't trust me?
أنت لا تثق بي؟
I just thought
لقد فكرت فقط
it was only my sister and I who knew it.
لم يكن أحد يعلم ذلك إلا أنا وأختي .
After I told you about it,
بعد أن أخبرتك بذلك،
- then... - Enough.
- إذن... - كفى.
I don't want to be hurt anymore.
لا أريد أن أتعرض للأذى بعد الآن.
You shouldn't have f*cking told me.
لا ينبغي لك أن تخبرني بذلك.
Where have Mathusorn and Karakade gone?
أين ذهب ماثوسورن و كاراكادي؟
I haven't seen them at all lately.
لم أراهم على الإطلاق في الآونة الأخيرة.
Kae is probably with them, asking the inmates to repay the money.
من المحتمل أن يكون كاي معهم، ويطلب من السجناء إعادة الأموال.
By the way, Mangpor,
بالمناسبة، مانجبور،
when will the new stock arrive?
متى سيصل المخزون الجديد؟
There.
هناك.
Huh?
هاه؟
You already dropped it off?
هل أسقطته بالفعل؟
I thought it'd be at the end of the month.
اعتقدت أنه سيكون في نهاية الشهر.
I'm not talking about the stock.
أنا لا أتحدث عن السهم.
It's the Rabid Dog.
إنه الكلب المسعور.
She must've found out the news about her sister.
يبدو أنها علمت بالأخبار عن أختها.
It's Kae who spread the news. I wasn't part of it.
كاي هو من نشر الخبر، ولم أكن طرفًا فيه.
- Don't do it! - Please, don't!
- لا تفعل ذلك! - من فضلك، لا تفعل ذلك!
- Hey! - Come with me.
- هيا! - تعال معي.
Wait...
انتظر...
What did you hear?
ماذا سمعت؟
- I've done nothing! - Silence!
- لم أفعل شيئا! - صمت!
Shut your mouth.
اصمت.
Just nod and play along.
فقط أومئ برأسك واستمتع باللعب.
Did she take the wrong person?
هل أخذت الشخص الخطأ؟
Shut the door.
أغلق الباب.
- Hey, you're not allowed in this area! - How did you get here?
- مهلا، أنت غير مسموح لك بالدخول إلى هذه المنطقة! - كيف وصلت إلى هنا؟
- You can't be here! - Leave now!
- لا يمكنك أن تكون هنا! - إذهب الآن!
- Out! - I told you to leave!
- اخرج! - لقد طلبت منك أن تغادر!
Hey, what the hell?!
مهلا، ماذا بحق الجحيم؟!
Hey! I told you that you're not allowed!
مهلا! لقد قلت لك أنه غير مسموح لك!
After them!
بعدهم!
Don't let them go!
لا تدعهم يذهبون!
I actually don't want to be here.
أنا لا أريد أن أكون هنا فعلا.
Incoming!
وارد!
The horse is climbing your leg!
الحصان يتسلق ساقك!
What the hell is going on?!
ماذا يحدث بحق الجحيم؟!
I've talked to inmate Mangpor.
لقد تحدثت مع السجين مانجبور.
This month, I'm selling the products from the prison myself.
هذا الشهر، سأقوم ببيع المنتجات من السجن بنفسي.
Right?
يمين؟
Are you crazy?
هل انت مجنون؟
How can you be sure you can do it?
كيف يمكنك التأكد من أنك قادر على القيام بذلك؟
It's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
Or do you want me to expose you, too?
أم تريدني أن أكشفك أيضًا؟
What the hell do you want?
ماذا تريد بحق الجحيم؟
Let me sell the products instead of her.
دعني أبيع المنتجات بدلاً منها.
I want permission to leave.
أريد الإذن بالمغادرة.
I only ask for this one time,
أنا أطلب هذا مرة واحدة فقط،
then I'll behave
ثم سأتصرف
and won't cause any more trouble.
ولن يسبب أي مشاكل أخرى.
Cause no more trouble?
لا تسبب المزيد من المشاكل؟
You already have.
لديك بالفعل.
The reports about Pa'Porn's Alzheimer's...
التقارير حول إصابة بابورن بالزهايمر...
Do you know how much trouble I'm in because of it?
هل تعلم حجم المتاعب التي أعاني منها بسبب ذلك؟
And you still dare ask me to go outside?
ومازلت تجرؤ على أن تطلب مني الخروج؟
All I ask for is this one time.
كل ما أطلبه هو هذه المرة الواحدة.
If I let you leave,
إذا سمحت لك بالمغادرة،
then you'll try running away.
ثم ستحاول الهروب.
Don't you dare beg me for anything
لا تجرؤ على التوسل إليّ من أجل أي شيء
because I'll never allow it.
لأنني لن أسمح بذلك أبدًا.
I'll also give you an increased sentence
سأعطيك أيضًا عقوبة مشددة
so that you'll stay here until you die.
لكي تبقى هنا حتى تموت.
Do you think you can just barge in here
هل تعتقد أنه يمكنك اقتحام هنا؟
and hope you get what you want?
وأتمنى أن تحصل على ما تريد؟
You're f*cking insane.
أنت مجنون تماما.
It's impossible.
إنه مستحيل.
Let go!
اتركه!
Sh*t...
ش*ت...
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
D*mn it.
لعنة عليك.
Put her in the hole for a month,
ضعها في الحفرة لمدة شهر،
so she doesn't fly off the handle.
حتى لا تفقد أعصابها.
Wouldn't that be too long?
ألا يعتبر ذلك وقتا طويلا؟
Obey my f*cking order!
أطيع أوامري اللعينة!
Let go of me!
أتركني!
- I told you to f*cking let go! - Move!
- لقد قلت لك أن تترك الأمر تمامًا! - تحرك!
You b*stard!
أيها الوغد!
Let me f*cking go!
دعني أذهب!
- Move! - Let go!
- تحرك! - اتركه!
Hands off.
ابتعد عن يديك.
Let me f*cking go, you b*stard!
دعني أذهب، أيها الوغد!
Let me go out!
دعني اخرج!
- Let go! - Enough!
-اتركه! -كفى!
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Let go!
اتركه!
- Let go! - She's so strong!
-اتركها! -إنها قوية جدًا!
- Hey, get in! - Let me go!
- مهلا، ادخل! - دعني أذهب!
She's so d*mn strong!
إنها قوية جدًا!
Hey, quickly!
مهلا، بسرعة!
Gosh...
يا إلهي...
She's impossibly strong.
إنها قوية بشكل لا يصدق.
- Let me go! - Whoa!
- دعني أذهب! - واو!
Kae.
أين؟
Hm?
هممم؟
Claire knew about her sister.
عرفت كلير عن أختها.
That's why she went mad and punched Wichai in the face.
لهذا السبب جن جنونها وضربت ويتشاي في وجهه.
She's being locked up alone for a month.
لقد تم حبسها بمفردها لمدة شهر.
For a month?
لمدة شهر؟
Good.
جيد.
This means she's no longer in my way.
وهذا يعني أنها لم تعد في طريقي.
She won't know that
انها لن تعرف ذلك
we're behind this, right?
نحن وراء هذا، أليس كذلك؟
Don't be afraid of her.
لا تخاف منها .
Claire
كلير
isn't as scary as we thought.
ليس مخيفًا كما كنا نظن.
Done?
منتهي؟
That's all you have for me?
هل هذا كل ما لديك بالنسبة لي؟
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Let me out!
دعني اخرج!
I told you to f*cking let me out!
لقد قلت لك أن تتركني أخرج!
Out!
خارج!
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Let go!
اتركه!
Sis, I'm hungry.
أختي أنا جائع.
Sis, I'm hungry...
أختي أنا جائع...
Sis...
نعم...
I'm hungry, sis.
أنا جائعة يا أختي.
D*mn it, Karakade!
D*mn it, Karakade!
Eat properly, please.
تناول الطعام بشكل صحيح من فضلك.
F*cking disgusting.
مقرف للغاية.
Do you want some?
هل تريد بعض؟
Oh?
أوه؟
I want a loan.
أريد قرضًا.
Are you for real?
هل انت حقيقي؟
Hey, Kae...
مهلا، كاي...
What should we do?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل؟
Your roommate wants to take a loan from us.
يريد زميلك في السكن أن يأخذ قرضًا منا.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
The interest rate is 20%.
معدل الفائدة هو 20%.
Repay us on payday.
سدد لنا يوم الدفع.
Pay it in one go.
ادفعها دفعة واحدة.
How much do you want?
كم تريد؟
Three thousand baht.
ثلاثة آلاف بات.
Why do you need that much money?
لماذا تحتاج إلى هذا القدر من المال؟
None of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
- Hey, you want trouble, don't you? - Duen.
- مهلا، أنت تريد المتاعب، أليس كذلك؟ - دوين.
Don't hurt our client.
لا تؤذي عميلنا.
When she can't afford to repay...
عندما لا تستطيع سداد...
we can deal with her later.
يمكننا التعامل معها لاحقًا.
Sis!
نعم!
Can I have a loan, please?
هل يمكنني الحصول على قرض من فضلك؟
You're talking too much.
أنت تتحدث كثيرا.
Hey, sis!
مهلا أختي!
I'm stuck.
أنا عالق.
I can't get my head out.
لا أستطيع إخراج رأسي.
It hurts!
إنه يؤلمني!
Guards! My head is bleeding!
يا حراس! رأسي ينزف!
- Help me. - I'm helping.
- ساعدني. - أنا أساعد.
Don't help her.
لا تساعدها.
Sis, I'm stuck!
أختي، أنا عالق!
I'll leave this to you, okay?
سأترك هذا لك، حسنًا؟
That's a lot.
هذا كثير.
Can you afford to repay them?
هل تستطيع أن تسدد لهم ديونك؟
Fast!
سريع!
Faster!
أسرع!
Hey, is this as fast as you can go?
مهلا، هل هذه هي السرعة التي يمكنك الذهاب بها؟
Come on! Faster!
هيا! أسرع!
Yeah.
نعم.
Bell.
جرس.
You can have the bags of soil and fertilizer,
يمكنك الحصول على أكياس التربة والأسمدة،
rose seeds, and gardening tools right away.
بذور الورد وأدوات البستنة على الفور.
The rest of your stuff is in the library.
باقي الأشياء موجودة في المكتبة.
Thank you, Mangpor.
شكرا لك مانجبور.
Mm, don't mention it.
مممم، لا تذكر ذلك.
[Bell]
[جرس]
[Claire]
[كلير]
Kung!
لو!
I'm out of liquor, Kung!
لقد نفذ مني الخمر، كونغ!
Kung! Kung!
إذا! إذا!
Kung!
لو!
I miss you so much!
أفتقدك كثيرًا!
Where have you been?!
أين كنت؟!
I'm out of liquor.
لقد نفد مني الخمر.
Please fetch some from my dad's.
من فضلك أحضر بعضًا من منزل والدي.
It's in his room.
إنه في غرفته.
- I'm not allowed in Mr. Sutthi's room. - Well, he's away!
- لا يُسمح لي بالدخول إلى غرفة السيد سوتي. - حسنًا، إنه بعيدًا!
- Please, fetch it for me. - Yes, Master!
- من فضلك، أحضره لي. - نعم يا سيدي!
Chop-chop!
تقطيع تقطيع!
You've got this!
لقد حصلت على هذا!
Like the wind, Kung!
مثل الريح ، كونغ!
Left, right, left, right, left, right!
يسار، يمين، يسار، يمين، يسار، يمين!
Score!
نتيجة!
- Yeah! - Top.
- نعم! - أعلى.
- Uh... - Jade, your name means a gemstone.
- أوه... - جاد، اسمك يعني حجر كريم.
Jade, your name means a gemstone!
جيد، اسمك يعني الأحجار الكريمة!
You're here to see Mr. Sutthi?
هل أنت هنا لرؤية السيد سوتي؟
He's not home. He's overseas.
إنه ليس في المنزل، إنه في الخارج.
He's probably going to be away for a long time.
من المحتمل أن يكون بعيدًا لفترة طويلة.
I'm actually coming to see you, Top.
أنا في الواقع قادم لرؤيتك، توب.
No, no, no! You're lying.
لا، لا، لا! أنت تكذب.
A person like you only serves my dad!
شخص مثلك يخدم والدي فقط!
You didn't come here to see me!
لم تأت إلى هنا لرؤيتي!
But now that you're here, let's drink!
ولكن الآن وقد وصلت إلى هنا، دعنا نشرب!
- Uh... - Drink!
- اه... - اشرب!
Top...
قمة...
There's nobody in the kitchen.
لا يوجد أحد في المطبخ.
I'm alone and have nobody else.
أنا وحدي وليس لدي أحد آخر.
You also put my girlfriend in prison.
لقد وضعت صديقتي في السجن أيضًا.
That's what I'm actually here for.
هذا هو السبب الحقيقي وراء وجودي هنا.
Right.
يمين.
Right!
يمين!
Ah...
اه...
You're spying on me or something?
هل تتجسس علي أم ماذا؟
The picture is so old, bro!
الصورة قديمة جداً يا أخي!
Found it!
وجدته!
Alright, let's go.
حسنا، دعنا نذهب.
Right now...
الآن...
- Right. - They...
- صحيح. - هم...
They're connecting the dots.
إنهم يربطون النقاط.
They found that people who got charged for drug abuse at the bar
لقد وجدوا أن الأشخاص الذين تم اتهامهم بتعاطي المخدرات في البار
were your friends.
كانوا أصدقائك.
To put it simply,
وبعبارة بسيطة،
the evidence is clear that you were there at the bar.
الدليل واضح على أنك كنت هناك في البار.
Aside from that, though...
وبصرف النظر عن ذلك، على الرغم من ذلك...
People online somehow discovered that...
لقد اكتشف الأشخاص عبر الإنترنت بطريقة ما أن...
your confiscated car key mysteriously went missing.
لقد اختفى مفتاح سيارتك المصادرة بشكل غامض.
Just get to the point already, brother.
لقد وصلت إلى النقطة بالفعل، يا أخي.
Soon, they'll be able to trace everything back to you.
وسوف يتمكنون قريبًا من إرجاع كل شيء إليك.
- Right. - However...
- صحيح. - ولكن...
You still have a way out.
مازال لديك طريق للخروج.
This will also get Bell out of prison.
وهذا سيؤدي أيضًا إلى إخراج بيل من السجن.
But you might have to cut ties
ولكن قد تضطر إلى قطع العلاقات
with your friends.
مع أصدقائك.
Uh...
أوه...
Thank you. I'm actually hungry.
شكرا لك. أنا جائع فعلا.
I want to give this to her and leave.
أريد أن أعطيها هذا وأرحل.
This is a restricted area.
هذه منطقة محظورة.
You're not allowed to enter.
لا يسمح لك بالدخول.
She has to stay there for a long time.
عليها أن تبقى هناك لفترة طويلة.
I think she's probably losing her mind.
أعتقد أنها ربما تفقد عقلها.
At least...
على الأقل...
Can you give this to her?
هل يمكنك أن تعطيها هذا؟
This will make her know that
وهذا سيجعلها تعرف أن
someone's waiting for her, even though she's in there alone.
هناك شخص ينتظرها، على الرغم من أنها هناك بمفردها.
I cannot allow that either.
لا أستطيع السماح بذلك أيضًا.
Your lunch.
غداءك.
I think you're going to enjoy this.
أعتقد أنك سوف تستمتع بهذا.
I'll never tell your secret to anyone.
لن أخبر أحدا بسرّك أبدًا.
Because I really care about you.
لأنني أهتم بك حقًا.
Please stop being mad at me
من فضلك توقف عن الغضب مني
and come out soon, okay?
وسيخرج قريبا، حسنًا؟
I'm waiting for you.
أنا في انتظارك.
Bell, I can't do this anymore.
بيل، لا أستطيع فعل هذا بعد الآن.
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
Wait...
انتظر...
I'll help.
سأساعدك.
Thank you. It must've been heavy.
شكراً لك. لا بد أنه كان ثقيلاً.
Don't forget to repay me, alright?
لا تنسى أن تسدد لي، حسنًا؟
Mm...
مم...
It's time to pay up, Bell.
لقد حان الوقت للدفع، بيل.
[Claire]
[كلير]
I haven't done any work at all,
لم اقم بأي عمل على الاطلاق
so I don't have any income.
لذلك ليس لدي أي دخل.
Everybody says that.
الجميع يقولون ذلك.
Can I at least pay the interest first?
هل يمكنني على الأقل سداد الفائدة أولاً؟
The principal is 3,000 baht,
رأس المال هو 3000 بات.
so 20% of that is 600 baht.
لذلك 20٪ من ذلك هو 600 بات.
I demand you pay the whole amount.
أطالبك بدفع المبلغ كاملاً.
I don't accept small payments.
لا أقبل المدفوعات الصغيرة.
The total amount isn't 3,000 baht either.
المبلغ الإجمالي ليس 3000 بات أيضًا.
It's 9,000 baht.
إنه 9000 بات.
It includes the bribe money that let you attend your dad's funeral...
وهو يشمل أموال الرشوة التي تمكنك من حضور جنازة والدك...
and your new shoes.
وحذائك الجديد.
If so, I can't repay you.
إذا كان الأمر كذلك، فلا أستطيع أن أسدد لك.
- You have... - Don't give her time.
- لديك... - لا تعطيها وقتاً.
You dare interrupt me?
هل تجرؤ على مقاطعتي؟
Yeah, so what?
نعم، ماذا في ذلك؟
She said she had no money.
قالت أنها ليس لديها مال.
Just collect the "interest" from her
فقط قم بتحصيل "الفائدة" منها
the same way you do with the others.
بنفس الطريقة التي تفعلها مع الآخرين.
It's not that difficult.
ليس الأمر صعبا.
You told us not to lay our fingers on her.
لقد طلبت منا عدم وضع أصابعنا عليها.
I've already withdrawn that condition.
لقد سحبت هذا الشرط بالفعل.
Claire is going to kill you all.
كلير سوف تقتلكم جميعا.
Let me tell you girls something.
دعوني أخبركم أيها الفتيات بشيء.
Don't be afraid of Claire.
لا تخف من كلير.
She's just an insane person.
إنها مجرد شخص مجنون.
She's never actually killed a person.
إنها لم تقتل أي شخص فعليا.
She's only serving the sentence for her sister.
إنها تقضي عقوبتها فقط عن أختها.
What the hell are you saying?
ماذا تقول بحق الجحيم؟
Surprised?
متفاجئ؟
I'm actually the one spreading the news about her sister.
أنا في الواقع من ينشر الأخبار عن أختها.
I eavesdropped on everything you two talked about
لقد تنصتت على كل ما تحدثتم عنه
and saw everything you did there.
ورأيت كل ما فعلته هناك.
Why are you doing this?
لماذا تفعل هذا؟
Because you two hurt my feelings.
لأنكما جرحتم مشاعري.
That's why I want my revenge.
لهذا السبب أريد الانتقام.
Can't I do that?
ألا يمكنني فعل ذلك؟
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
Make her pay.
اجعلها تدفع الثمن.
Don't be afraid of Claire.
لا تخف من كلير.
Mathusorn.
ماثوسورن.
Karakade.
كاراكادي.
Lock her arms.
قفل ذراعيها.
- Hey! Hey! - Let me go.
- هي! هي! - دعني أذهب.
Come here!
تعال الى هنا!
Stay still!
ابقى ساكنا!
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
Teach her a lesson,
علمها درسا
so she learns.
لذلك تتعلم.
Why can't I interrupt you, huh?
لماذا لا أستطيع مقاطعتك، هاه؟
What should we do?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل؟
That's enough. She's gonna die.
هذا يكفي، سوف تموت.
Let's go, girls.
هيا بنا يا فتيات.
Come on, let's move.
هيا، دعنا نتحرك.
After her.
بعدها.
- Come on! - May I ask for an interview?
- تعال! - هل يمكنني أن أطلب مقابلة؟
D*mn it.
لعنة عليك.
Can I please have an interview?
هل يمكنني إجراء مقابلة من فضلك؟
- May I ask for an interview? - Natty.
- هل يمكنني أن أطلب مقابلة؟ - ناتي.
There is news reporting that
هناك تقارير إخبارية تفيد بأن
- you're part of a murder case. - Calm down, everyone.
- أنت جزء من قضية قتل. - اهدأوا جميعًا.
- What are your thoughts on this? - Calm down, everybody.
- ما رأيك في هذا؟ - اهدأوا يا رفاق.
Please calm down.
من فضلك اهدأ.
- Please step back. - Do you have anything to say?
- من فضلك تراجع إلى الوراء. - هل لديك أي شيء لتقوله؟
Can we please have an interview?
هل يمكننا إجراء مقابلة من فضلك؟
Hey!
يا!
You!
أنت!
This way!
من هنا!
Hurry!
عجل!
Get in!
أدخل!
Stop!
قف!
Quickly!
بسرعة!
Come on, get in!
تعال، ادخل!
- Can I have an interview? - After her!
- هل يمكنني إجراء مقابلة؟ - بعدها!
Please wait!
انتظر من فضلك!
May we ask for an interview?
هل يمكننا أن نطلب مقابلة؟
Natty, please wait!
ناتي، من فضلك انتظر!
- Natty!
- ناتي!
- Can we please have an interview? - Natty...
- هل يمكننا إجراء مقابلة من فضلك؟ - ناتي...
Natty.
ناتي.
Feel free to drop me off here.
لا تتردد في تركي هنا.
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
Wait.
انتظر.
Yes?
نعم؟
Remember, we've met before?
هل تتذكر أننا التقينا من قبل؟
We were there to visit the same inmate
كنا هناك لزيارة نفس السجين
whose name is Claire.
التي اسمها كلير.
Wait, don't leave!
انتظر، لا تغادر!
- Talk to me. - Let me go!
- تحدث معي. - دعني أذهب!
I'm done talking!
لقد انتهيت من الحديث!
Hey!
يا!
You're free.
أنت حر.
The roses are blooming just in time to welcome you back.
الورود تتفتح في الوقت المناسب للترحيب بك مرة أخرى.
I've been changing the fertilizer,
لقد قمت بتغيير الأسمدة،
using compost and manure back and forth.
استخدام السماد العضوي والروث ذهابًا وإيابًا.
I've also been watering them daily.
لقد كنت أسقيهم أيضًا يوميًا.
Who did this to you?
من فعل بك هذا؟
Was it Deedee's girls?
هل كانوا فتيات ديدي؟
Or was it Kae?
أم كان كاي؟
Claire!
كلير!
Don't do it!
لا تفعل ذلك!
Please don't.
من فضلك لا تفعل ذلك.
I don't want to lose you again.
لا أريد أن أخسرك مرة أخرى.
Please, I beg you.
من فضلك، أتوسل إليك.
- Wait... - Duen.
- انتظر... - إنه كذلك.
Over there.
هناك.
Don't be scared of her.
لا تخف منها.
She's never actually killed anyone.
إنها لم تقتل أحدا على الإطلاق.
I know you're behind all this sh*tty stuff,
أنا أعلم أنك وراء كل هذه الأشياء السيئة،
including the news about my sister
بما في ذلك الأخبار عن أختي
and how Bell got hurt.
وكيف أصيب بيل.
Do you know
هل تعلم
what Bell told me?
ماذا قال لي بيل؟
She told me not to do anything to you,
لقد قالت لي أن لا أفعل لك أي شيء،
even after all that you did to her.
حتى بعد كل ما فعلته لها.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
don't mess with Bell and me ever again.
لا تعبث معي ومع بيل مرة أخرى.
Or else, the first person I kill
وإلا فإن أول شخص أقتله
will be you.
سوف تكون انت.
Got it?
فهمتها؟
And about the money Bell owed you,
وأما عن المال الذي كان بيل يدين لك به،
I'll find the money and repay you myself.
سأبحث عن المال وسأسدده لك بنفسي.
See? I warned you.
أرأيت؟ لقد حذرتك.
It doesn't matter if she has
لا يهم إذا كان لديها
or hasn't killed anyone,
أو لم يقتل أحدا،
she's still the Rabid Dog.
إنها لا تزال كلبًا مسعورًا.
You're so f*cking dumb.
أنت غبي جدًا.
F*ck off!
إذهب إلى الجحيم!
How dare you f*cking say that to me?!
كيف تجرؤ على قول هذا لي؟!
- How could you say that?! - So what?
- كيف تقول ذلك؟! - وماذا في ذلك؟
So what?!
وماذا في ذلك؟!
- Let me go! - Get off me!
- دعني أذهب! - ابتعد عني!
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
I'm fully taking over the business.
أنا أتولى العمل بشكل كامل.
You dare do that?
هل تجرؤ على فعل ذلك؟
Yeah!
نعم!
Turn around and ask your underlings.
استدر واسأل مرؤوسيك.
Just f*cking look at them!
فقط انظر إليهم!
Let me ask you this.
دعني أسألك هذا.
What the f*ck do you even do in a day?
ماذا تفعل في يوم واحد؟
The money funding the business is mine.
الأموال التي تمول الأعمال التجارية هي ملكي.
When the payment's due,
عندما يحين موعد الدفع،
Karakade and Mathusorn handle collecting.
كاراكادي وماثوسورن يتعاملان مع عملية الجمع.
Those who do more deserve to be paid more.
من يبذل المزيد من الجهد يستحق أن يحصل على المزيد من الأجر.
Those who do less deserve to be paid f*cking less!
أولئك الذين يفعلون أقل يستحقون أن يحصلوا على أجر أقل بكثير!
Kae!
أين!
You piece of sh*t...
أنت قطعة من القرف...
You're such an a**hole.
أنت مثل هذا الأحمق.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Don't hurt my sister!
لا تؤذي أختي!
Without Dao and Wichai,
بدون داو وويتشاي،
it kinda feels empty, huh?
إنه يشعر بالفراغ نوعًا ما، أليس كذلك؟
Don't f*cking do it, Kae!
لا تفعل ذلك أيها اللعين، كاي!
What?
ماذا؟
Let her go!
اسمح لها أن تذهب!
Are you going to cry?
هل ستبكي؟
Don't f*cking touch her!
لا تلمسها أيها اللعين!
I told you to stop!
لقد قلت لك أن تتوقف!
Kae!
أين!
Kae! You b*stard!
كاي! أيها الوغد!
- Kae! - What the f*ck do you want, huh?
- كاي! - ماذا تريد بحق الجحيم، هاه؟
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
How dare you do this to me?
كيف تجرؤ على فعل هذا بي؟
I'm really sorry.
انا آسف حقا.
Don't say f*cking sorry!
لا تقل آسفًا على الإطلاق!
Go f*cking away!
إذهب بعيدا عن اللعنة!
Get out!
اخرج!
Oh, really?
أوه حقًا؟
Mr. Elephant, I'm doing well.
السيد الفيل، أنا بخير.
Have you had anything?
هل لديك أي شيء؟
Are you out of your mind?!
هل أنت خارج عن عقلك؟!
You put an inmate in confinement for a month?
هل وضعت سجينًا في الحبس لمدة شهر؟
Well...
حسنًا...
That inmate punched me, sir.
لقد ضربني هذا السجين، سيدي.
Then extend her sentence
ثم مدد عقوبتها
and file a report.
وتقديم تقرير.
You can't simply take action so arbitrarily.
لا يمكنك اتخاذ إجراء تعسفيًا بهذه البساطة.
Do you understand what humanity is?
هل فهمت ما هي الإنسانية؟
You f*cking reported your punishment to the Director?
هل قمت بإبلاغ المدير بالعقوبة التي تعرضت لها؟
Yes.
نعم.
I did it.
أنا فعلت هذا.
That's only the first report about you, though.
هذا هو فقط التقرير الأول عنك.
There are still more reports to come
لا يزال هناك المزيد من التقارير القادمة
from accepting bribe money
من قبول أموال الرشوة
and the affair
والقضية
- between... - Enough. Shut up.
- بين... - كفى. اسكت.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Transfer Bell to my cell,
نقل الجرس إلى هاتفي المحمول،
and I'll be out of your hair.
وسوف أكون خارج شعرك.
What else do you want?
ماذا تريد ايضا؟
That's all.
هذا كل شئ.
Fine.
بخير.
♫There's a problem that needs to be resolved♫
???هل هناك مشكلة تحتاج إلى حل؟؟؟
♫You came into my life and made me sway♫
???لقد دخلت إلى حياتي وجعلتني أتأرجح؟؟؟
♫I'm a bit lost and don't know what to say,♫
???أنا تائه قليلاً ولا أعرف ماذا أقول,؟؟؟
♫But simply looking into your eyes makes me fall apart (all bark, no bite)♫
???ولكن مجرد النظر في عينيك يجعلني أتفكك (كل النباح، لا عض) ???
♫I'm husky for your love♫
???أنا أجش من أجل حبك؟؟؟
♫You turn a rabid wolf into a pug♫
???هل تحول الذئب المسعور إلى كلب صغير؟؟؟
♫Say bow, wow, wow, wow, wow♫
???قل قوس، واو، واو، واو، واو؟؟؟
♫You make a hunter turn sweet♫
???هل تجعل الصياد يتحول إلى حلو؟؟؟
♫Sweet on you only♫
???حلو عليك فقط؟؟؟
♫The only one I've given in to♫
???الشخص الوحيد الذي استسلمت له؟؟؟
♫Never been like this before♫
???لم أكن مثل هذا من قبل؟؟؟
♫Hug me every day and night♫
???عانقني كل يوم وليلاً؟؟؟
♫Let me stay by your side♫
???دعني أبقى بجانبك؟؟؟
[Dao, Duen, Deedee]
[داو، دوين، ديدي]
Have you ever thought of going outside?
هل فكرت يوما بالخروج؟
Outside the cell or the prison?
خارج الزنزانة أم السجن؟
Outside the prison, of course.
خارج السجن بالطبع.
Um...
واحد...
At first, I did,
في البداية، فعلت ذلك،
but not anymore.
ولكن ليس بعد الآن.
Don't you feel any resentment
ألا تشعر بأي استياء؟
for serving time for a crime you didn't commit?
لقضاء فترة عقوبة بسبب جريمة لم ترتكبها؟
It's what I've chosen,
هذا ما اخترته
so I have to accept the consequences.
لذلك يجب علي أن أتقبل العواقب.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
Ever since I got to stay here,
منذ أن وصلت إلى هنا،
it's been bad for me.
لقد كان سيئا بالنسبة لي.
I haven't been able to sleep that well at all.
لم أتمكن من النوم بشكل جيد على الإطلاق.
All I feel is paranoia.
كل ما أشعر به هو جنون العظمة.
However, I do hope that there's a way to turn my case around.
ومع ذلك، آمل أن تكون هناك طريقة لتغيير حالتي.
I want to get out of here so badly.
أريد الخروج من هنا بشدة.
What if I never get to be free?
ماذا لو لم أحصل على الحرية أبدًا؟
Why did you say that?
لماذا قلت ذلك؟
I've exchanged my life for my sister's.
لقد استبدلت حياتي بحياة أختي.
If my freedom
إذا حريتي
meant she had to be locked up here instead...
يعني أنه كان يجب حبسها هنا بدلاً من ذلك ...
I just can't accept that.
لا أستطيع قبول ذلك.
♫You turn the darkness around♫
???أنت تقلب الظلام؟
♫Making me fall deeply for you♫
???تجعلني أقع في حبك بعمق؟؟؟
♫Making me fearless from within♫
???تجعلني لا أخاف من الداخل؟؟؟
♫Dark grey skies of yesterday♫
???سماء رمادية داكنة من الأمس؟؟؟
♫Turned differently today♫
???تغيرت اليوم بشكل مختلف؟؟؟
♫When you're right here, alright♫
???عندما تكون هنا، حسنًا؟؟؟
♫You're my starlight, shine bright♫
???أنت ضوء نجمتي، تتألق بشكل ساطع؟؟؟
♫Even in the nights where no star shines♫
???حتى في الليالي التي لا يوجد فيها نجم لامع؟؟؟
♫You change this empty world♫
???هل تغير هذا العالم الفارغ؟؟؟
♫And reveal what love looks like♫
???وأكشف كيف يبدو الحب؟؟؟
♫My starlight, you're my life♫
???ضوء نجمتي، أنت حياتي؟؟؟
♫Just hold me tight♫
???فقط احتضني بقوة؟؟؟
♫No matter how dark the night is,♫
"مهما كان الليل مظلما"
♫You're like the star that lights up my sky♫
???أنت مثل النجم الذي يضيء سمائي؟؟؟
♫No matter how dark the night is,♫
"مهما كان الليل مظلما"
♫You're like the star that lights up my sky♫
???أنت مثل النجم الذي يضيء سمائي؟؟؟